{
    "id": "4445d65d2f4f4ea4b8ee54c05f22883d",
    "title": "Possessive Pronouns And Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She claimed that the money was ............................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Some students have left ................................ notebooks in the class.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never been to ............................... home.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither Sam nor Peter can remember ............................ passwords.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She told me that the bag was ................................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been to their home several times but they have never been to ..................................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "our",
                "ours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She found .............................. passport but we couldn't find ...............................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her, our",
                "hers, ours",
                "her, ours"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a lot of friends but none of them was invited for ........................... birthday.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I think this pen is ................................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him if he had seen ............................. key.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked him what he was doing in ............................. room",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can show you my ID. Can I see ................................?",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}